Kettle Idol
Okay, kettle-kun, we have a main section for you.
I'd like to talk about the main project, Cute.
Do you know what cute is?
I want to look cute.
Please!
Please call the title.
My three main elements.
Great!
Thank you very much.
Let's go!
This is a corner where we ask you to introduce the three elements that make up who you are.
This corner is for you to get to know our guest idols better!
May I start with the three elements?
Yes, please.
First, a dog.
One, dog.
Two, very hot.
Three, sleep.
I see! The elements that make up Mr. Nakamura are
1. dog
2. hot and spicy
And third, sleep, is that right?
Yes, sir.
Next time notice
First, a dog.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
The dog has a puppy at home.
Oh, my God.
I love him so much that I can't live without this picture of him.
All the recordings on my phone are of dogs.
What breed is he?
A pug and a cavalier.
How long have you had dogs in your life?
The dog is a very recent addition.
Oh, they came recently?
Yes, they are.
Oh, so he's a little dog?
He's not even a year old yet.
Oh, he's so cute.
Super cute.
Is it a one-year-old male or female?
Male.
A male?
Yes, a male.
Uh, what's your name, if you don't mind me asking first?
Jake.
Cool!
Jake?
It doesn't come from that.
It's a dog with a pointy chin.
Why do you have a jaw like that, Jake?
Why Jake? He's got a pointy chin.
We called him Shaq at first.
Just kidding.
We called him Shaq.
And then we were like, "Let's pick a proper name.
Then we decided on a proper name.
I changed Shaq a little bit and called him Jake.
I called him Jake, and he responded for the first time.
So we decided to call him Jake.
And the dog itself...
You mean you thought this was my destiny?
Yes.
Well, if you don't mind, can I take a look?
I wonder how long he'll last.
But you're always so cute when we take pictures.
The handsomest one.
The handsomest one?
Yes, yes, yes, yes... just the one I love the most.
I mean...
Usually.
Which one?
Usually he's squat like this.
I see.
He's cute.
When you look at him from the front, his teeth stick out.
But when I take his picture, he looks so cute.
Dogs like that are the best for now.
I'll miss you when you're here on business.
I miss him.
That's why I don't mind if you send me videos every day.
You have him send you videos?
Yes, I do.
Well, that's good, because I can see them.
So who do you think J.Y. Park is the most attached to in the house?
I'm sorry, but he's most attached to his father.
He's a father.
Most often it's his mom.
Dads.
When he's lying down.
She feels really comfortable playing on top of him.
She climbs on top of him.
I'm sure he's tired of me by now.
It's frustrating, but he's so cute.
He's so cute when he comes over sometimes.
He's so cute.
If you were a shrimp, you'd be Mirei.If it were in Ebichu, Mirei would be the one.
Mirei Senpai
Mirei senpai
Mirei Senpai is
This program was made up of Takuya-san, Nakamura-san's guess, Masa-san
Mr. Makoo, Mr. Ojipei, and
Yudanari Norio provided this program.
Thank you very much.